A Guide to the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Executive Journals 1992
Library of Virginia
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 23 (Box 2, Folder 190)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 191)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 28 (Box 2, Folder 192)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 193)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 194)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 3 (Box 2, Folder 195)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 196)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 197)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 25 (Box 2, Folder 198)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 26 (Box 2, Folder 199)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 200)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 201)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 202)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 13 (Box 2, Folder 203)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 17 (Box 2, Folder 204)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 20 (Box 2, Folder 205)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 206)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 207)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 10 (Box 2, Folder 208)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 17 (Box 2, Folder 209)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 210)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 211)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 212)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 213)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 214)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 11 (Box 2, Folder 215)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 15 (Box 2, Folder 216)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 18 (Box 2, Folder 217)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 218)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 219)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 220)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 1 (Box 2, Folder 221)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 28 (Box 2, Folder 222)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 July 31 (Box 2, Folder 223)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 224)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 3 (Box 2, Folder 225)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 September 9 (Box 2, Folder 226)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 227)
- Addendum, Appointments, Oaths, 1992 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 228)
- List of Contents, 1992 January-February (Box 3, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Commutation of death sentence, 1992 January 23, Herbert Russell Bassette AKA Herbert Russell Bassett (Box 3, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 9, Vicky Mae McCool AKA Vicki Mae McCool AKA Victoria Johnson (Box 3, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 14, Morris, Stephanie L. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 14, Wickline, Paul Anthony (Box 3, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 21, Moore, Walter Clay (Box 3, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 21, Speller, Elmer Linwood (Box 3, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 28, Kirkham, Ronald John, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 28, Bearden, Teddy Glyn (Box 3, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 28, Conley, James K. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 28, Walton, Robert Bailey, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 27, Woltz, Robert Walter (Box 3, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 January 28, Hunt, Raheem (Box 3, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Oswald Clyde Thompson AKA "Do-right" (Box 3, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Johnson, Wesley Duane (Box 3, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Wolcott, Stacey Kathleen (Box 3, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Hebert, Patrick Andrew (Box 3, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Justice, Kenny Lee (Box 3, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Hicks, Carl Littleton (Box 3, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Beverly Ann Gaddis AKA Beverly Ann White (Box 3, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Lightfoot, Jimmy (Box 3, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Bailey, Dennis (Box 3, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Picurro, Joseph F. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 10, Madson, Mark Stewart (Box 3, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 14, Grace, John L., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 15, Disario, Paschal (Box 3, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 9, Brown, Michael N. E. (Box 3, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 20, William Anthony, Jr. AKA William Slade AKA Anthony Slade (Box 3, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 20, Hamilton, Pierre C. (Box 3, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 20, Forest, Barry Craig (Box 3, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 27, Lane, John M., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 27, Suzuki, Naoko Sue (Box 3, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 27, Beverly, Charles, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 27, Staha, Wayne A., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Adkins, Randall Lee (Box 3, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Guilliams, Charles David (Box 3, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Kevin Owen Smith AKA K. O. Smith (Box 3, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Wilson, Ronald Blaine (Box 3, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Hicks, Floyd Cecil, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Vinsh, Charles Thomas (Box 3, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Banks, Robert O'Neal (Box 3, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Ross, Rickey Lee (Box 3, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Joan Elizabeth Lane AKA Joan Elizabeth Morris (Box 3, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, White, Billy Reed (Box 3, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Eugene Roy Budd AKA Roy Budd (Box 3, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Wood, Roy Allen (Box 3, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Jerrell Stanton Leadman, Jr. AKA Jerrell Staunton Leadman, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, Mahler, George Lewis (Box 3, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 January 23, MacIntyre, Stuart Ellsworth (Box 3, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 6, Wilcox, Gary S. (Box 3, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 6, Ward, John Edward (Box 3, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 11, Hundley, David T. (Box 3, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 11, Henderson, Michael (Box 3, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 11, Delando Celley AKA Delando Maurice Culley (Box 3, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 14, Harris, Dewey L. (Box 3, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 14, Joseph Lee Banks AKA Johnny Edward Coffey (Box 3, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 17, Pladsen, Kenneth N., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 17, Moore, Vernon Ray (Box 3, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 20, Tullis, Bryan Scott (Box 3, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 27, Lucas, Ricky D. (Box 3, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 27, Newman, Colin K. (Box 3, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 February 27, Shields, Wilba Sue (Box 3, Folder 62)
- List of Contents, 1992 February-March (Box 4, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 6, Malson, Monica Lee (Box 4, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 6, Lee, Anthony (Box 4, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 12, Dower, Albert Monroe, III (Box 4, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 13, McKinney, Annie Michelle (Box 4, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 13, Swann, Mark David (Box 4, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 13, Pace, Tanya E. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 13, Fowler, Thomas Norman (Box 4, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 13, Phipps, Robert (Box 4, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 14, Rhoades, Jerry Wayne (Box 4, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Dockery, Michael Lynn (Box 4, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Cornman, Dennis Howard (Box 4, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Webb, Stanley Eugene, III (Box 4, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Christine Juliano AKA Christine Vaughn (Box 4, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Lyles, Forest Elmer (Box 4, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Blair, Joseph Henry (Box 4, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 19, Hershey, Michele Rene (Box 4, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 27, Abul-Karim Akbar Bilal AKA Clifford Woodrow Billips AKA Earnest James Holliman (Box 4, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 27, Imhoff, Douglas G. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 27, Stewart, Kenneth Spencer (Box 4, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 February 27, Oberle, Douglas Raymond (Box 4, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 19, Taylor, Alphonzo, Sr. (Box 4, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 19, Morrison, Roosevelt (Box 4, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Jean Gough Hackney AKA Margaret Jean Shults (Box 4, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Ricks, Cynthia Marie (Box 4, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Tyler, Douglas Leroy, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Billingsley, Ronald Charles (Box 4, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Little, Billy Franklin (Box 4, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Carol Elizabeth Chaplin Castle AKA Carol Elizabeth Chaplin (Box 4, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 February 20, Haga, William Harry, Jr. (Box 4, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 3, Hartman, Della (Box 4, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 3, Panetta, David Joseph (Box 4, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 3, Watson, Rodney L. (Box 4, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 4, Lyon, David William (Box 4, Folder 34)
- RESTRICED: Rendition, 1992 March 4, Davidson, Charles Roger AKA Charles Roger Davison (Box 4, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 10, McMillion, Terri Len (Box 4, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 10, Murphy, Theresa Leggan (Box 4, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 10, Watkins, Troy Jerome (Box 4, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 11, Overstreet, Ronald Lee (Box 4, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 11, Lisa Dawn Counce AKA Heather Johnson AKA Lynn Frank (Box 4, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 11, Bark, Paul R. (Box 4, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 11, Alvin Winston AKA Jon Edward Gholson (Box 4, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 11, O'Farril, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 13, Peter M. Hall AKA Steven Carter AKA Michael Hart AKA Pee Wee (Box 4, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 19, Marquez, Clayton (Box 4, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 March 27, Shirley A. Davis AKA Sharon Williams AKA Shirley Davis AKA Shirley Butler AKA Shirley Williams (Box 4, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 2, Schimanski, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 2, Martin, Douglas W. (Box 4, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 2, Smith, Donald Wayne (Box 4, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 9, Blackley, Joseph Rezel (Box 4, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 January 20, Brown, Michael Norman Edward (Box 4, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 9, Brian Doran AKA Brian Eric Doran (Box 4, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 9, Tommy Davis AKA Eddie Dean (Box 4, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 11, Roughton, William K. (Box 4, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 12, Martin, Raymond R. (Box 4, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Wells, John Willie, III (Box 4, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Wright, Joseph Jay (Box 4, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Denchfield, Eric R. (Box 4, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Hendricks, Jerry Lee (Box 4, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Nguyen, Trung Duc (Box 4, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 20, Renaud, Fawn Marie (Box 4, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 27, Goolsby, Garland Miles (Box 4, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 March 27, Randolph O'Dell Boardwine AKA Randy Boardwine (Box 4, Folder 63)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, White, Jimmy Lewis (Box 4, Folder 64)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, Marina Claire Simmons AKA Marina Claire Schwabacher (Box 4, Folder 65)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, Linda Jean Riker AKA Linda Jean Flaherty (Box 4, Folder 66)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, Smith, Jerry Wayne (Box 4, Folder 67)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, Coward, Clarence William, Sr. (Box 4, Folder 68)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 March 24, Ernest Wayne Meeks, Sr. AKA Earnest Wayne Meeks (Box 4, Folder 69)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1992 April-May (Box 5, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 1, Clark, Adam Joseph (Box 5, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 1, Sweat, Robert Warren (Box 5, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 3, Cachoian, Gerard (Box 5, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 3, Sheila Christmas AKA Sheila Holmes (Box 5, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 8, Cynthia D. Goodman AKA Cindy (Box 5, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 8, Castleman, David Lee (Box 5, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 8, William C. Dyer AKA Carl W. Dyer, Sr. (Box 5, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 15, Joseph L. Jobe AKA Joseph Lann Jobe (Box 5, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 15, Harris, Paul Roderick (Box 5, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 15, Gerald Jeffrey Sykes AKA Geraldo Jeffrey Sykes, Sr. AKA G. J. Sykes (Box 5, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 October 10, Juanita Kirkland AKA Anita Kirkland AKA Juanita Bolton AKA Anita Bolton (Box 5, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 23, Owens, Regina Lee (Box 5, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 23, Seaton, Michelle (Box 5, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 23, Wry, Charles (Box 5, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 April 30, Daniel Benzing AKA Daniel Lee Benzing (Box 5, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 6, Greer, Dennis Ray (Box 5, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 6, Spriggs, Carlos John (Box 5, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 6, Poole, Craig (Box 5, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 6, John W. Higdon AKA John Wesley Higdon (Box 5, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 7, Miller, Harvey Lee (Box 5, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 8, Shackleford, Dallas (Box 5, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 8, Jackson, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 10, Fred Eugene Blevins AKA Fred Blevins AKA Freddie E. Blevins (Box 5, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 13, Coy, Jermey Elwood (Box 5, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 13, Martin, Michael Joseph (Box 5, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 17, Hubbard, Joan Alice (Box 5, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 27, Smith, Kirk Stanley (Box 5, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 27, Drewry, Troy Lynn (Box 5, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 28, Shortt, Vikki R. (Box 5, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 28, Barce, James W. (Box 5, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 28, Queen, Timothy L. (Box 5, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 28, Wiggs, Reginald (Box 5, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 29, Kapalka, Wayne (Box 5, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 29, Johnny Javen Page AKA "Jay" AKA "J.J." (Box 5, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 29, Smith, John B., Jr. (Box 5, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 13, Anthony Dwayne Meadows AKA Clifford Johnson (Box 5, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 13, Jamie Jo Adkins AKA Jamie Jo Adkins Webb (Box 5, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 13, Elaine Owens AKA Mary Elaine Owens (Box 5, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 19, Michael Clemens AKA Michael Todd Clemens AKA Michael Timothy Ferguson (Box 5, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 19, Dipalma, Ames (Box 5, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 19, Reynolds, Brian Thomas (Box 5, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 19, Manning, Gary Watkins (Box 5, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 19, Luis S. Acosta AKA Alcola Pedro (Box 5, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 28, Chinoskey William Johnson, Jr. AKA William Johnson (Box 5, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 28, Weiss, Steven Carey (Box 5, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 28, Taylor, Henry L., Jr. (Box 5, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 May 28, Warner, Earl Randall (Box 5, Folder 48)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 14, Rodriguez, Rebecca Garcia (Box 5, Folder 49)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 12, Shabazz, Markus Beyah (Box 5, Folder 50)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 12th, Kazarian, Clifford (Box 5, Folder 51)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 12, Kenneth Maples AKA Kenneth Wayne Maples (Box 5, Folder 52)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 12, Carter, Annie Renee (Box 5, Folder 53)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 12, Lawson, Bryan Neil (Box 5, Folder 54)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 14, Shupe, William Edward (Box 5, Folder 55)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 14, Diaz, Daniel H. (Box 5, Folder 56)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 19, Grimes, William Preston, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 57)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 19, Keo, Chek W. (Box 5, Folder 58)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 19, Armour, Gordon Greg (Box 5, Folder 59)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 21, John Nathaniel Sanders AKA John Martin Alston (Box 5, Folder 60)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 25, Isaacs, Thomas J. (Box 5, Folder 61)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 May 25, Abdul Abdulwahhab AKA Abdul Sadig Abdulwahhab (Box 5, Folder 62)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 May 5, Woodruff, Harvey Claude, Jr. (Box 5, Folder 63)
- RESTRICTED: List of Contents, 1992 June (Box 6, Folder 1)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 3, Jones, Penny (Box 6, Folder 2)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 3, Thomas, Kirk Alan (Box 6, Folder 3)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 4, Rye, Larry Clayton (Box 6, Folder 4)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 16, Eddie Ray Crites AKA Eddie R. Crites (Box 6, Folder 5)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 16, Stephen Wolinsky AKA Ted Stephen Wolinski (Box 6, Folder 6)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 23, Kooshian, Bart (Box 6, Folder 7)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 25, Moore, Lonnie (Box 6, Folder 8)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 25, Clairburn Dooley AKA Claiburn R. Dooley (Box 6, Folder 9)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 25, Patrell, David Allen (Box 6, Folder 10)
- RESTRICTED: Rendition, 1992 June 25, Thornton, Phillip A. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 3, Susan Hudak AKA Susan Lynn White (Box 6, Folder 12)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Ford, Harry Lewis (Box 6, Folder 13)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Reid, Sean M. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Christian, Patricia Ann (Box 6, Folder 15)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Jolley, Tara Konjolka (Box 6, Folder 16)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Maxwell, Kenneth Lamont (Box 6, Folder 17)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 5, Roberts, James Clinton (Box 6, Folder 18)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 8, Margaret Ann Cutlip AKA Margaret Ann Briganti AKA Margaret Ann West AKA Margaret Ann Webb (Box 6, Folder 19)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 8, Bigley, Shellie Annell (Box 6, Folder 20)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 8, Traxler, Bradley Jerome (Box 6, Folder 21)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 July 6, Colbert, John H., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 22)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 8, Blackstock, David M. (Box 6, Folder 23)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 11, Rattliffe, Malcolm D. (Box 6, Folder 24)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 15, Isherwood, Karen Lynn (Box 6, Folder 25)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Street, Mark Anthony (Box 6, Folder 26)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Lawson, James Randall (Box 6, Folder 27)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Phillips, W.T. (Box 6, Folder 28)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Doyle, Robert Francis (Box 6, Folder 29)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Booher, Alfred, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 30)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Lucas, Troy Cleveland (Box 6, Folder 31)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Thompson, Darrell K. (Box 6, Folder 32)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Hayes, Bradley Alan (Box 6, Folder 33)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 April 8, Terry, Otis L. (Box 6, Folder 34)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 17, Williams, Tanisha Ann (Box 6, Folder 35)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Carey, Karen (Box 6, Folder 36)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Donnie Dougal AKA Donald A. Dougal (Box 6, Folder 37)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Carey, Joel (Box 6, Folder 38)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Raymond, Yvette Louise (Box 6, Folder 39)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Colby, Warren A., IV (Box 6, Folder 40)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Barber, Michael Randolph (Box 6, Folder 41)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Edwards, Cedric Charles (Box 6, Folder 42)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Dale, George Oscar (Box 6, Folder 43)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, Weston, Ronnie Lee (Box 6, Folder 44)
- RESTRICTED: Requisition, 1992 June 22, O'Neal, Michael (Box 6, Folder 45)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, Landolt, Kevin Eugene (Box 6, Folder 46)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, White, Carroll William (Box 6, Folder 47)
- RESTRICTED: Restoration of Rights, 1992 June 12, James Dearmont Dodson AKA Junior D. Dodson (Box 6, Folder 48)